{
  "endTime": -1,
  "numTeams": 1,
  "teams": [
    {
      "password": "asdf",
      "score": 0,
      "teamName": "Admin Team",
      "correctAnswers": []
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the third crossed out word in the MFA Contemporary Art neon sign?",
      "answer": "eat",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the audio tour ID number for Monet’s Water Lilies?",
      "answer": "853",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What sacred art form does Lalla Essaydi make use of in her photograph in the \"Women Take the Floor\" exhibit?",
      "answer": "calligraphy",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many pieces of glassware are in the McElheny display?",
      "answer": "48",
      "points": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In this iconic harbor scene by John Singleton Copley, how many people are in the boat?",
      "answer": "9",
      "points": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What material is the blue lion in the Nubia exhibit made of?",
      "answer": "faience",
      "points": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist uses styrofoam cups to engage with the architecture of the MFA? (Last name only)",
      "answer": "donovan",
      "points": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Around what year was the MFA's most famous sculpture of Guanyin, the Bodhisattva of Compassion, made?",
      "answer": "1200",
      "points": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Placed near John Singer Sargent’s potentially most famous work is a painting by Obama’s portraitist. What is the last name of the artist whose work inspired Obama’s portraitist for this painting?",
      "answer": "dobson",
      "points": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "This artist’s upside down chandelier was not originally going to stay in the MFA, but was kept due to its wide popularity. (Artist’s last name only)",
      "answer": "chihuly",
      "points": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Samuel McIntire was commissioned to produce a gilded statue of an eagle for a house in Salem, Massachusetts. What is the house number of that house?",
      "answer": "70",
      "points": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Old Testament figure is portrayed in Sargent's oil sketch for the Boston Public Libray murals?",
      "answer": "moses",
      "points": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the last name of the American artist who designed a statue of a flower seller from a massively popular novel of his time?",
      "answer": "rogers",
      "points": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The bowl which is a declaration of political defiance would have been used for what kind of alcohol?",
      "answer": "rum",
      "points": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The ruler in this statue, who may be Oba Esigie or even Prince Oranmiyan, ruled over what region?",
      "answer": "benin",
      "points": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "This mirror in which you can’t see yourself was inspired by what Shakespeare play?",
      "answer": "othello",
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What household tool is CeCe McDonald carrying in her 2016 portrait by Andrea Bowers?",
      "answer": "hammer",
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "The MFA’s oldest piece of art is estimated to have been made in 6400 BC. What animal is it shaped like?",
      "answer": "hare",
      "points": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "The statue of this Lady originally stood in either the family tomb at Asyut or in a sanctuary in Southern Egypt, but was later transported to the tomb of Kerma's last ruler.",
      "answer": "sennuwy",
      "points": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "One room in the MFA contains a depiction of itself. What is the last name of the artist who produced that work?",
      "answer": "prosperi",
      "points": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the mask with exaggerated eyes used in the coming of age traditions of the Democratic Republic of the Congo?",
      "answer": "gitenga",
      "points": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first name of the knight depicted in this kneeling statue, which is set in front of an early 15th century stained glass window?",
      "answer": "alonso",
      "points": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "This piece, which contains Mexican, Spanish-Islamic, and Chinoiserie elements, contains depictions of the first free black settlement in Mexico. What is the surname of the family who owned this estate?",
      "answer": "rivandeneira",
      "points": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of slip glaze does the pitcher possibly depicting Toussaint L'Ouverture use?",
      "answer": "albany",
      "points": 10
    }
  ]
}
